<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Desmond David, LLC]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Desmond David, LLC]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/desmond-david/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 01:23:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/desmond-david/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 01:23:34 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Desmond David, LLC</strong></p>,<p><strong>Phone (201) 321-4316</strong></p>,<p><strong>Email:&nbsp;<a href="mailto:Info@DesmondDavid.com">Info@DesmondDavid.com</a></strong></p>,<p><strong></strong></p>,<p><strong>Who and What We Are:</strong></p>,<p>Here at Desmond David we are a one stop shop, dedicated, digital strategy, online original content strategists and content copywriters content provider.&nbsp;</p>,<p>We're a well-respected interactive digital media and social medial agency located in downtown New York City.&nbsp; We are best know for our deep strategic thinking skills and work with and along side of &nbsp;many meaningful and high-profile clients to create integrated, comprehensive web experiences that span across channels (web, mobile and social).</p>,<p>&nbsp;Words alone simply just can’t define us.&nbsp; Our Vision is to tell vivid, memorable stories that are targeted to inform and engage the customer’s end client. Our team works hands on with our clients, taking complex ideas and turning them into compelling narrative s that drive actions and delivers end results.</p>,<p>We possess the strategic writing talents that are both wordsmith ad idea generators. &nbsp;Our content writers are digital natives who understand how design and content come together to tell a better story with fewer words… a story that will be told across both operation, sales and client channels in many different forms including text, imagery and video.</p>,<p><strong>The people who work for Desmond David and its founders all possess the following shared traits.</strong></p>,<p><strong>Strategically.</strong>&nbsp;We apply deep research and critical thinking to create integrated, comprehensive content strategies.</p>,<p><strong>Creatively.</strong>&nbsp;We bring passion to our work and produce content strategies, campaigns and copy that engage, motivate, and inspire.</p>,<p><strong>Curiously.</strong>&nbsp;We ask great questions, enjoy learning about new things, and are always looking to grow.</p>,<p><strong>Cleverly.</strong>&nbsp;We’re quick on our feet, think outside the box, and have original ideas and imagination.</p>,<p><strong>Confidently.</strong>&nbsp;We are friendly, professional and poised, whether in simply brainstorming with our team, running meetings, or delivering client presentations.</p>,<p><strong>Friendly.</strong>&nbsp;We work well with both our and your teams, contribute ideas in a positive manner, and are great listeners.</p>,<p><strong>Passionately.</strong>&nbsp;Most of all we love what you do, giving you, the client, everything you've got, and are continually seeking ways to improve our craft.</p>,<p><strong>Innovation is at the core of our colleague relationships and our client work – not just for the sake innovation, but to elevate the users’ experience and exceed our clients’ goals.</strong></p>,<p>We’ve been doing this right for our clients for the least ___ years and can hit the ground running.</p>,<p>We’ve written for large. major, distinct brands across a variety of industries and audiences.</p>,<p>We have a deep understanding of the various digital channels, including social media, SEO and email. Even better, we appreciate the strengths of each platform and can adapt content accordingly.</p>,<p>We have expertise in client discovery, market research, and competitive analysis, realizing that these are the foundation of creating comprehensive and integrated content strategies.</p>,<p>We are able to create compelling content strategies and campaigns that drive conversions.</p>,<p>We can engage with potential clients to understand their unique needs and help shape proposals that win.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/desmond-david/desmond-david-llc/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a423aafe-28a4-431c-9e41-a387a70844f2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 17:17:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>